ITAI MIZLISH

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

CONTACT



+97254-2258899



itaim148@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/itai-mizlish/



https://github.com/itaim18



www.itaimiz.com

EDUCATION

Bachelor in Science in Computer Science

JCT Lev Academic Center

2015 - 2019

CERTIFICATES

The complete 2022 Web development Bootcamp.

React - The Complete Guide.

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Masterclass

udemy

SKILLS

- React
- JavaScript & ES6
- HTML
- CSS
- Sass
- Node.js
- · MongoDB (mongoose and studio 3T)
- Firebase
- express
- · Responsive design
- Tailwind

PROFILE

I am a highly motivated Front-end Developer and web developer with a strong understanding of React.js, its methods and hooks. Experienced in **building front-end and full-stack architectures** from scratch. Proficient in UI/UX through CSS tools (Sass, Tailwind, Bootstrap). Knowledge of DS implementation and algorithms solving in JavaScript and ES6. A Computer Science graduate in highschool and a self learner.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer

2022 - present

- Design and create architectures for web applications.
- Develop full-stack web apps using MERN structure and firebase.
- Use Javascript libraries, CSS and Sass to create user interfaces.
- · Experience in functional programming in JavaScript and knowledgeable in ES6.

Tutor 2016 - 2018

Israeli Center for Advancement in Math (associated with Bar Ilan University)

- Facilitated annual Science Day activities for children.
- Tutored basic Physics and Aeronautics lessons in schools in the TA Metropolitan Area.
- · Graded tests and tutored children with special needs.

Military Service

2019 - 2022

Infantry Unit

Volunteering

2015 - 2018

Krembo Wings

· Assisted and accompanied children with special needs and formed unique connections with them.

LANGUAGES

English

Hebrew

